Finding Aid for the Alberto Sánchez de Iriarte Collection [Spanish Civil War]
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series III: Magazine Fragments, Spain 1914-1936
  - A-E
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 151-154, October 2, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 159-162, November 13, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 55-60, December 4, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 107-110, December 25, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 39-44, February 19, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 65-70, April 9, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 143-146, April 30, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 109-112 and 141-144, May 7, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 129-132, May 14, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 39-48, May 21, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 63-66, June 4, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 95-96, July 23, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 199-202, October 22, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 207-210, November 12, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 34-35 and 60-65, November 19, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 34-35, November 26, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 46-55, 86-89, 118-121, and 189-190, December 3, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 31-32, December 10, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 46-51, December 31, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 21-22, January 14, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 87-94 and 149-152, February 18, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 79-84, April 22, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 117-120, 123-124 and 149-154, May 13, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 83-88, May 27, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 87-92, June 24, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Blanco y Negro (White and Black), pgs. 99-102, July 15, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Brisas (Breezes,) “Soller”, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Crónica (Chronicle), April 14, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Crónica (Chronicle), October 30, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Crónica (Chronicle), November 20, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Crónica (Chronicle), January 28, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Crónica (Chronicle), May 12, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Crónica (Chronicle), September 9, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Crónica (Chronicle), October 28, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Crónica (Chronicle), July 14, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Crónica (Chronicle), November 24, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Cultura (Culture) pgs. 27-30, September 15, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Don Quijote Votando (Don Quixote, Voting), April 8, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - El Viajero (The Traveler) pgs. 21-24, August 1933 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - El Viajero (The Traveler) pgs. 13-1`6, December 1933 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - El Viajero (The Traveler), April 1934 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - El Viajero (The Traveler), May 1934 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - El Viajante de Comercio (The Traveling Salesman), pgs. 15-16 and 31-38, February 1931 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - El Viajante de Comercio (The Traveling Salesman), pgs. 25-26, January 1932 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - El Viajante de Comercio (The Traveling Salesman), pgs. 33-34, May 1932 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - El Viajante de Comercio (The Traveling Salesman), pgs. 23-40, February 1933 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - El Viajante Español (The Spanish Traveler) pgs. 5-6 and 23-24, March 1931 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Estampa, pgs. 19-20, September 12, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Estampa, pgs. 43-44, February 27, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Estampa, pgs., 1-6 and 13-14, September 17, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Estampa, pgs. 7-10, November 19, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Estampa, pgs. 19-20 and 23-24, December 31, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Estampa, pgs. 21-28, February 11, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Estampa, pgs. 15-18, 21-22, and 33-34, April 22, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Estampa, pgs. 7-10 and 13-14, May 13, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Estampa, pgs. 7-12, May 20, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Estampa, pgs. 19-20, June 10, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Estampa, pgs. 11-14, July 15, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Estampa, pgs. 7-10, November 11, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Estampa, pgs. 17-18, November 25, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Estampa, pgs. 7-10 and 47-48, December 23, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Estampa, pgs. 3-10 and 23-26, January 20, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Estampa, pgs. 23-26, February 17, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Estampa, pgs. 19-20, March 17, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Estampa, pgs. 13-14, May 5, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Estampa, pgs. 9-12, May 12, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Estampa, pgs. 13-14 and 23-28, May 19, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Estampa, pgs. 12-13 and 23-26, June 23, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Estampa, pgs. 26-27, June 30, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Estampa, pgs. 3-6 and 37-38, July 7, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Estampa, October 27, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - E-V and French Magazine Fragments, C-N
    - E-V
      - Estampa, July 13, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Estampa, August 3, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Estampa, August, 10, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Estampa, August, 17, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Estampa, pgs. 7-10 and 13-16, August, 24, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Estampa, August, 31, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Estampa, September 7, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Estampa, pgs. 1-2, January 11, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Estampa, pgs. 21-24, March 14, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Estampa, pgs. 47-48, March 28, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Estampa, pgs. 23-25 and 33-40, April 4, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Estampa, pgs. 33-36, April 11, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Estampa, pgs. 13-16, 25-28 and 44-45, July 4, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Estampa, Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Fallas, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Gaceta de la Bolsa y de la Propiedad, La interesante declaración ministerial del Gabinete Lerroux al Parlamento (Stock and Property Gazette, The interesting ministerial declaration of Lerroux’s Cabinet to Parliament), pgs. 673-674, December 20, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Gaceta de la Bolsa y de la Propiedad (Stock and Property Gazette), pgs. 457-458, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Hojas Selectas (Selected Sheets), pgs. 715-720 and 727-734, July, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Hojas Selectas (Selected Sheets), pgs. 867-876 and 947-952, August, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Iberia, “Mallorca”, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - La Actualidad, pgs. 1-2, August 8, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - La Esfera (The Sphere), pgs. 5-8, August 21, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - La Esfera (The Sphere), pgs. 17-18, November 13, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - La Esfera (The Sphere), pgs. 11-12, November 20, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - La Esfera (The Sphere), pgs. 11-12, December 4, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - La Esfera (The Sphere), pgs. 11-12, December 18, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - La Esfera (The Sphere), Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - La Nueva Democracia (The New Democracy), pgs. 2-6, April, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Mercurio, Revista Comercial Ibero-Americana (Mercury, Latin American Trade Magazine), pgs. 345-348, November 13, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Metrópolis, March 1931 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Metrópolis, pgs., April-May 1931 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 15-16, January 5, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 15-16, January 12, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 3-8 and 13-14, February 24, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 5-8 and 15-16, March 16, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 3-10, April 20, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 15-16, May 9, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 11-14, April 26, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 21-24, September 13, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 7-8, November 22, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), pgs. 20-21, September 12,1934 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Mundo Gráfico (Graphic World), Undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs. 39-40, November 21, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs. 3-6,9-10,19-22 and 27-28, March 25, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs. 3-8 and 33-36, September 2, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs. 35-38, September 9, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs. 7-8 and 17-18), June 16, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs. 19-22, October 13, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs. 7-8, November 17, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs. 19-22, December 22, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs. 17-18, December 28, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - Nuevo Mundo (New World), pgs., Undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - Obras, Revista de Construcción (Works, Construction Magazine), pgs. 299-306, September, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - Obras, Revista de Construcción (Works, Construction Magazine), pgs. 107-114, March, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      - Obras, Revista de Construcción (Works, Construction Magazine), pgs. 157-164, April, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - Obras, Revista de Construcción (Works, Construction Magazine), pgs. 243-248, June, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - Revista de las Españas (Magazine of the Spains) pgs. 513-520 and 523-530, October-December 1930 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - Revista de las Españas (Magazine of the Spains) pgs. 503-510, October-December 1934 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Semblanza de Santiago Rusiñol (Portrait of Santiago Rusiñol) pgs., Undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Touring Club, July, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Valencia Atracción (Valencia Attraction), pgs. 39-46, March, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Valencia Atracción (Valencia Attraction), pgs. 65-66 and 73-74, May, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - Valencia Atracción (Valencia Attraction), pgs. 91-94, June, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Vida Gallega, Aniversario de Rosalía Castro (Galician Life, Anniversary of Rosalía Castro), Undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Fragments in French C-N 1907-1934
      - Chambre Française de Commerce et d’Industrie de Madrid, Janvier a Grenade (French Chamber of Commerce and Industry, January in Granade), January, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Le Crapouillot, Magazine Clipping, France, December 1, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Les Annales, pgs. 129-130, France, August 11, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - Les Annales, pgs. 217-220, France, September 8, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 68)
      - Les Annales, pgs. 409-410, 415-416, 419-420 and 427-428, France, November 3, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 69)
      - Les Annales, pgs. 589-592 and 601-604, France, December 22, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 70)
      - Les Annales, pgs. 470, 481-484, 489-490 and 493-496, France, November 21, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      - Les Annales, pgs. 81-92, France, October 25, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 72)
      - Noel, pgs. 17-18, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Series IV: Magazine Fragments, Latin America, 1907-1942
  - CA-CR
    - Carteles (Cartels), pgs. 19-22, Cuba, November 23, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Continental, pgs. 9-12, Latin America, May 1916 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 1916 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 1917 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Cromos, pgs. 29-30, Colombia, July 21, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Cromos, pgs 85-88, Colombia, August, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Cromos, pgs. 147-148, Colombia, September 15, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Cromos, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Cromos, pg.s 259-262, Colombia, May 18, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Cromos, pgs. 329-330, Colombia, June 15, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Cromos, pgs. 161-162, Colombia, September 21, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Cromos, pgs. 243-246, Colombia, October 26, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 2, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Cromos, Colombia, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 23, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Cromos, pgs. Colombia, September 27, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Cromos, pgs. Colombia, November 22, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Cromos, pgs. Colombia, December 6, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Cromos, pgs. 93-94, Colombia, February 21, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Cromos, pgs. 131-132, Colombia, March 13, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Cromos, pgs. 225-226, Colombia, May 1, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Cromos, pgs. 253-254, Colombia, May 8, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Cromos, pgs. 269-272, Colombia, May 15, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Cromos, pgs. 395-398, Colombia, July 10, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Cromos, pgs. 43-44, Colombia, July 31, 1920` (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Cromos, pgs. 75-76, Colombia, August 14, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Cromos, pgs. 85-86, Colombia, August 21, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Cromos, pgs. 105-106, Colombia, August 28, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Cromos, pgs. 113-114, Colombia, September 4, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Cromos, pgs. 139-142, Colombia, September 11, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Cromos, pgs. 145-146, Colombia, September 18, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Cromos, pgs. 177-178, Colombia, October 2, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Cromos, pgs. 193-194, Colombia, October 9, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Cromos, pgs. 214-215, Colombia, October 16, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Cromos, pgs. 225-226, Colombia, October 23, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Cromos, pgs. 241-242, Colombia, October 30, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 5, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 5, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 18, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 2, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Cromos, Colombia, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Cromos, Colombia, January 31, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 18, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 4, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 18, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 25, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 22, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 29, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 6, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 20, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 10, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 17, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 24, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 1, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 13, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 15, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 22, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 29, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 19, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Cromos, Colombia, September 16, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 14, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 21, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 28, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 4, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 18, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 25, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Cromos, Colombia, December 2, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Cromos, Colombia, December 9, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 3, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 10, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 17, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 31, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 14, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 21, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 5, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 12, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 26, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 9, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 16, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 23, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 8, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 11, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 25, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Cromos, Colombia, September 8, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 20, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 27, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 10, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 24, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Cromos, Colombia, December 1, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Cromos, Colombia, December 7, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Cromos, Colombia, December 22, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Cromos, Colombia, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 92)
- Series IV: Magazine Fragments, Latin America, 1907-1942
  - Cromos-E
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 9, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 8, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 29, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 19, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 10, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 31, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 14, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 21, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 19, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 16, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Cromos, Colombia, September 13, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Cromos, Colombia, September 27, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 4, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 11, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Cromos, pgs. 281-284, Colombia, October 25, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Cromos, pgs. 309-310, Colombia, November 8, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 22, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Cromos, pgs. 29-32, Colombia, December 20, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 7, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 14, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 28, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 4, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 11, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Cromos, pgs. 309-310, Colombia, May 2, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 13, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 25, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 1, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 8, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 22, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Cromos, pgs. 193-194, Colombia, August 29, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Cromos, Colombia, September 12, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Cromos, pgs. 245-246, Colombia, September 19, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Cromos, pgs. 305-306, Colombia, October 10, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 31, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 21, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Cromos, Colombia, December 19, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 6, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 13, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 7, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 5, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 12, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 26, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 3, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 10, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 16, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 13, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 27, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Cromos, Colombia, December 4, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Cromos, Colombia, December 28, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 19, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 19, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 2, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Cromos, Colombia, April 16, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 14, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 21, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 2, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 16, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 27, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Cromos, Colombia, September 24, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 15, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Cromos, Colombia, January 7, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Cromos, Colombia, January 14, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 11, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 5, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 23, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 17, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 30, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Cromos, Colombia, January 31, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 7, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Cromos, Colombia, March 14, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 2, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Cromos, Colombia, June 6, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 4, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Cromos, Colombia, August 29, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 1931 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 7, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Cromos, Colombia, February 6, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Cromos, Colombia, July 8, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 31, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Cromos, Colombia, December 29, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Cromos, Colombia, May 23, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Cromos, Colombia, October 3, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 14, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 12, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Cromos, Colombia, November 19, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Cromos, Colombia Arts and Literature, Undated (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Crónica Teatral, (Theatrical Chronicle), Latin America, Undated (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - De Gandía, Enrique, “Historia e Historiosofía,” Nosotros ( History and Historiosophy, Us Magazine), pgs. 140-153, Argentina, August 1943 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - De Soiza Reilly, Juan José, “La nueva emoción en la Historia Argentina,” Colombia (The New Emotion of Argentinian History, Columbia magazine), Brazil, July 1, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - El Economista Uruguayo, “El impuesto único” (The Uruguayan Economist, Single Tax), pgs. 5-10, Uruguay, April 2, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 90)
- Series IV: Magazine Fragments, Latin America, 1907-1942
  - E-Z
    - El Gráfico (The Graphic), Colombia, July 8, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 1)